const qMagooshBank = [
    {
        question: "Abash",
        answers: [
            "to make ashamed; to embarrass", 
            "Poison; torment; cause of harm", 
            "completely obvious", 
            "to object or show reluctance"
        ],
        correct: "to make ashamed; to embarrass",
        questionId: "0001",
        description:"Meredith felt abashed by her inability to remember her lines in the school chorus of 'Old McDonald Had a Farm'."
    },
    {
        question: "Bane",
        answers: ["rhythm; the rise and fall of sounds", "Poison; torment; cause of harm","completely obvious", "to object or show reluctance"],
        correct: "Poison; torment; cause of harm",
        questionId: "0002",
        description:"To say that someone is the bane of your existence is to say that that person poisons your enjoyment of life."
    },
    {
        question: "Cadence",
        answers: ["without any attempt at concealment", "Poison; torment; cause of harm", "rhythm; the rise and fall of sounds", "to object or show reluctance"],
        correct: "rhythm; the rise and fall of sounds",
        questionId: "0003",
        description:"We wished the tone of Irwin's words would have a more pleasing cadence, but he spoke in a dull monotone."
    },
    {
        question: "Daunt",
        answers: ["Poison; torment; cause of harm", "rhythm; the rise and fall of sounds", "to object or show reluctance", "to make fearful; to intimidate"],
        correct: "to make fearful; to intimidate",
        questionId: "0004",
        description:"The steepness of the mountain daunted the team of amateur climbers, who hadn't realized what they were in for."
    },
    {
        question: "Efface",
        answers: ["to erase; to rub away the features of", "rhythm; the rise and fall of sounds", "to make fearful; to intimidate", "to object or show reluctance"],
        correct: "to erase; to rub away the features of",
        questionId: "0005",
        description:"The inscription on the tombstone had been effaced by centuries of weather."
    },
    {
        question: "Fetter",
        answers: [ "without any attempt at concealment", "to restrain, to hamper", "completely obvious", "to make fearful; to intimidate"],
        correct: "to restrain, to hamper",
        questionId: "0006",
        description:"In his pursuit of the Noble Prize for physics, Professor Jenkins was fettered by his near total ignorance of the subject."+
        "To be unfettered is to be unrestrained or free of hindrances."
    },
    {
        question: "Gratuitous",
        answers: ["without any attempt at concealment", 
        "to restrain, to hamper", 
        "given freely; unjustified; unprovoked; uncalled for",
         "to make fearful; to intimidate"],
        correct: "given freely; unjustified; unprovoked; uncalled for",
        questionId: "0007",
        description:"The scathing review of the movie contained several gratuitous remarks about the sex life of the director."
    },
    {
        question: "Hermetic",
        answers: ["without any attempt at concealment", 
        "given freely; unjustified; unprovoked; uncalled for", 
        "to object or show reluctance", 
        "impervious to external influence; airtight"],
        correct: "impervious to external influence; airtight",
        questionId: "0008",
        description:"The poisonous substance was sealed hermetically inside a glass cylinder."
    },
    {
        question: "Idiosyncrasy",
        answers: ["a peculiarity; an eccentricity", 
        "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
        "given freely; unjustified; unprovoked; uncalled for", 
        "a maze; something like a maze"],
        correct: "a peculiarity; an eccentricity",
        questionId: "0009",
        description: "Eating green beans drenched in ketchup for breakfast was one of Jordana's idiosyncrasies."
    },
    {
        question: "Labyrinth",
        answers: [
        "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
        "a maze; something like a maze",
        "without any attempt at concealment", 
        "clumsy"],
        correct: "a maze; something like a maze",
        questionId: "0010",
        description: "Each of the fifty floors in the office building was a labyrinth of dark corridors and narrow passageways."
    },
    {
        question: "Malfeasance",
        answers: [
        "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
        "without any attempt at concealment",
        "an illegal act, especially by a public official", 
        "a maze; something like a maze"],
        correct: "an illegal act, especially by a public official",
        questionId: "0011",
        description: "President Ford officially pardoned former president Nixon before the latter could be convicted of any malfeasance."
    },
    {
        question: "Narcissism",
        answers: [
        "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
        "an illegal act, especially by a public official", 
        "a maze; something like a maze",
        "excessive love of one's body or oneself"],
        correct: "excessive love of one's body or oneself",
        questionId: "0012",
        description: "Someone who suffers from narcissism is said to be narcisssistic."+
        " The selfish students were bound up in narcissistic concerns and gave no thought to other people."
    },
    {
        question: "Obfuscate",
        answers: ["to darken; to confuse; to make confusing", 
        "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
        "without any attempt at concealment", 
        "clumsy"],
        correct: "to darken; to confuse; to make confusing",
        questionId: "0013",
        description: "The spokeman's attempt to explain what the president had meant merely obfuscated the issue further."+
        " People had hoped the spokesman would elucidate."
    },
    {
        question: "Painstaking",
        answers: ["dishonorable", 
        "extremly careful; taking pains", 
        "an illegal act, especially by a public official", 
        "to modify or restrict"],
        correct: "extremly careful; taking pains",
        questionId: "0014",
        description: "We made a painstaking effort to move the piano without harming it;"+
        " first we wraped it in Kleenex, then we covered it with "+
        "balloons, then we put it on roller skates and pushed it down the ramp."
    },
    {
        question: "Qualify",
        answers: ["extremly careful; taking pains", 
        "an illegal act, especially by a public official", 
        "to modify or restrict", 
        "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
        correct: "to modify or restrict",
        questionId: "0015",
        description: "Susan qualified her praise of Judith by saying that her kind words applied"+
        " only to Judith's skillful cooking and not to her abhorrent personality."
    },
    {
        question: "Rapacious",
        answers: ["extremly careful; taking pains", 
        "an illegal act, especially by a public official", 
        "dishonorable", 
        "greedy; plundering; avaricious"],
        correct: "greedy; plundering; avaricious",
        questionId: "0016",
        description: "Wall Street investment bankers are often accused of being rapacious,"+
        " but they claim they are performing a valuable economic function. The noun form is rapacity."
    },
    {
        question: "Sacrosanct",
        answers: ["sacred; held to be inviolable", 
        "greedy; plundering; avaricious", 
        "dishonorable", 
        "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
        correct: "sacred; held to be inviolable",
        questionId: "0017",
        description: "A church is sacrosanct. So, for Chiristians, is belief in the divinity of Jesus Christ."
    },
    {
        question: "Tangential",
        answers: ["extremly careful; taking pains", 
        "only superficially related to the matter at hand; not especially relevant; peripheral", 
        "greedy; plundering; avaricious", 
        "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
        correct: "only superficially related to the matter at hand; not especially relevant; peripheral",
        questionId: "0018",
        description: "The mayor's speech bore only a tangential relationship to the topic that had been announced."
    },
    {
        question: "Unctuous",
        answers: ["dishonorable", 
        "unsure how to act or react", 
        "oily, both literally and figuratively; insincere", 
        "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
        correct: "oily, both literally and figuratively; insincere",
        questionId: "0019",
        description: "Salad oil is literally unctuous. A used card salesman might be figuratively unctuous- "+
        "that is, oily in the sense of being slick, sleazy, and insincere."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Vacillate",
        answers: ["greedy; plundering; avaricious", 
        "unsure how to act or react", 
        "exclude from a community or group", 
        "to be indecisive; to waver"],
        correct: "to be indecisive; to waver",
        questionId: "0020",
        description: "We invited James to spend Thanksgiving with us, but he vacillated fo so long about whether he would be able to come that we finally"+
        "became annoyed and disinvited him."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Wanton",
        answers: ["malicious; unjustifiable; unprovked; agregious", 
        "to be indecisive; to waver", 
        "exclude from a community or group", 
        "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
        correct: "malicious; unjustifiable; unprovked; agregious",
        questionId: "0021",
        description: "Terrorists commit wanton acts on a helpless populace to make their point."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Zealous",
        answers: ["dishonorable", 
        "enthusiastically devoted to something; fervent", 
        "exclude from a community or group", 
        "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
        correct: "enthusiastically devoted to something; fervent",
        questionId: "0022",
        description: "The zealous young policeman made so many arrests that the city jail soon became overcrowded."
    }
    ,
    // foreign words and phrases
    {
        question: "A propos",
        answers: ["malicious; unjustifiable; unprovked; agregious", 
        "to be indecisive; to waver", 
        "to the purpose; to the point; pertinent", 
        "for a particular purpose; only for the matter at hand"],
        correct: "to the purpose; to the point; pertinent",
        questionId: "0023",
        description: "A comment is a propos (or apropos) if it is exactly appropriate for the situation."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Ad hoc",
        answers: ["malicious; unjustifiable; unprovked; agregious", 
        "to be indecisive; to waver", 
        "to the purpose; to the point; pertinent", 
        "for a particular purpose; only for the matter at hand"],
        correct: "for a particular purpose; only for the matter at hand",
        questionId: "0024",
        description: "An ad hoc committee is a committee established for a particular purpose, or to deal with a particular problem."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Aficionado",
        answers: ["fan", 
        "to be indecisive; to waver", 
        "exclude from a community or group", 
        "black beast; something or someone that one avoids or strongly dislikes"],
        correct: "fan",
        questionId: "0025",
        description: "An aficionado of football is a football fan. An afficionado of theater is a theater fan."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Al fresco",
        answers: ["malicious; unjustifiable; unprovked; agregious", 
        "in the fresh air; outside; in the fresh air", 
        "exclude from a community or group", 
        "black beast; something or someone that one avoids or strongly dislikes"],
        correct: "in the fresh air; outside; in the fresh air",
        questionId: "0026",
        description: "An al fresco meal is a picnic."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Au courant",
        answers: ["malicious; unjustifiable; unprovked; agregious", 
        "to be indecisive; to waver", 
        "in the current; up to date; informed", 
        "black beast; something or someone that one avoids or strongly dislikes"],
        correct: "in the current; up to date; informed",
        questionId: "0027",
        description: "To be au courant is to know all the latest information."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Bete noire",
        answers: ["malicious; unjustifiable; unprovked; agregious", 
        "to be indecisive; to waver", 
        "in the current; up to date; informed", 
        "black beast; something or someone that one avoids or strongly dislikes"],
        correct: "black beast; something or someone that one avoids or strongly dislikes",
        questionId: "0028",
        description: "If you absolutely despised your landlord, you might say that he was your bete noire."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Deja vu",
        answers: ["already seen; an illusory feeling of having seen or done something before", 
        "to be indecisive; to waver", 
        "in the current; up to date; informed", 
        "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
        correct: "already seen; an illusory feeling of having seen or done something before",
        questionId: "0029",
        description: "To have deja vu is to believe that one has already done or seen what one is in fact doing or seeing for the first time."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "De facto",
        answers: ["head to head; a private conversation between two people", 
        "from the fact; actual", 
        "in the current; up to date; informed", 
        "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
        correct: "from the fact; actual",
        questionId: "0030",
        description: "Your de facto boss is the person who tells you what to do."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Laissez-faire",
        answers: ["head to head; a private conversation between two people", 
        "from the fact; actual", 
        "let do; a doctrine of noninterference by government in the economoy; noninterference in general", 
        "my fault"],
        correct: "let do; a doctrine of noninterference by government in the economoy; noninterference in general",
        questionId: "0031",
        description: ""
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Mea culpa",
        answers: ["head to head; a private conversation between two people", 
        "from the fact; actual", 
        "let do; a doctrine of noninterference by government in the economoy; noninterference in general", 
        "my fault"],
        correct: "my fault",
        questionId: "0032",
        description: "Mea culpa mea culpa. I was the one who put the dog in the cat's bed."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Tete-a-tete",
        answers: ["head to head; a private conversation between two people", 
        "face to face; in relation to; compared with", 
        "let do; a doctrine of noninterference by government in the economoy; noninterference in general", 
        "my fault"],
        correct: "head to head; a private conversation between two people",
        questionId: "0033",
        description: "The two attorneys resolved their difference in a brief tete-a-tete before the trial began."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Vis-a-vis",
        answers: ["head to head; a private conversation between two people", 
        "face to face; in relation to; compared with", 
        "let do; a doctrine of noninterference by government in the economoy; noninterference in general", 
        "my fault"],
        correct: "face to face; in relation to; compared with",
        questionId: "0034",
        description: "The students' relationship vis-a-vis the administration was one of confrontation."
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Zeitgeist",
        answers: ["head to head; a private conversation between two people",  
        "let do; a doctrine of noninterference by government in the economoy; noninterference in general", 
        "time spirit; the spirit of the times",
        "my fault"],
        correct: "time spirit; the spirit of the times",
        questionId: "0035",
        description: "Bill was always out of step with the zeitgeist; he had short hair in 1970 and long hair in 1980."
    }
    // ,
    // {
    //     question: "",
    //     answers: ["head to head; a private conversation between two people",  
    //     "let do; a doctrine of noninterference by government in the economoy; noninterference in general", 
    //     "time spirit; the spirit of the times",
    //     "my fault"],
    //     correct: "",
    //     questionId: "0036",
    //     description: ""
    // }
    // ,
    // {
    //     question: "",
    //     answers: ["head to head; a private conversation between two people",  
    //     "let do; a doctrine of noninterference by government in the economoy; noninterference in general", 
    //     "time spirit; the spirit of the times",
    //     "my fault"],
    //     correct: "",
    //     questionId: "0036",
    //     description: ""
    // }
    // ,
    // {
    //     question: "",
    //     answers: ["head to head; a private conversation between two people",  
    //     "let do; a doctrine of noninterference by government in the economoy; noninterference in general", 
    //     "time spirit; the spirit of the times",
    //     "my fault"],
    //     correct: "",
    //     questionId: "0036",
    //     description: ""
    // }
];
    
    export default (n = 5) =>
        Promise.resolve(qMagooshBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
      
    